{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 6)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + (x + 6) \u003d (x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + (x + 6) - (x + 5) \u003d 0\n(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 6) + 1/(x + 1) \u003d (x + 5)/(x + 6)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)\n2(3x + 1) + 2(x + 2) \u003d (3x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(3x + 1) + 2(x + 2) - (3x + 1) \u003d 0\n5(x + 1) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(x + 2) + 2/(3x + 1) \u003d 1/(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 3)\n(x + 3) + (x + 1) \u003d (3x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 3) + (x + 1) - (3x + 2) \u003d 0\n(-x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 1/(x + 3) \u003d (3x + 2)/(x + 1)(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 7)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + (3x + 7) \u003d 3(x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + (3x + 7) - 3(x + 2) \u003d 0\n(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(3x + 7) + 1/(x + 1) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(3x + 7)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 4)(x + 2)\n3(x + 2) + (x + 4) \u003d (3x + 7)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 2) + (x + 4) - (3x + 7) \u003d 0\n(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(x + 4) + 1/(x + 2) \u003d (3x + 7)/(x + 4)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 7)(x + 2)\n2(x + 2) + 3(3x + 7) \u003d (3x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 2) + 3(3x + 7) - (3x + 1) \u003d 0\n8(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(3x + 7) + 3/(x + 2) \u003d (3x + 1)/(3x + 7)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 5)(2x + 3)\n2(2x + 3) + (x + 5) \u003d (2x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(2x + 3) + (x + 5) - (2x + 5) \u003d 0\n3(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(x + 5) + 1/(2x + 3) \u003d (2x + 5)/(x + 5)(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 7)(3x + 4)\n3(3x + 4) + 3(2x + 7) \u003d (x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(3x + 4) + 3(2x + 7) - (x + 5) \u003d 0\n14(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(2x + 7) + 3/(3x + 4) \u003d (x + 5)/(2x + 7)(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 1)(2x + 5)\n(2x + 5) + 3(2x + 1) \u003d 2(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 5) + 3(2x + 1) - 2(x + 1) \u003d 0\n6(x + 1) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(2x + 1) + 3/(2x + 5) \u003d 2(x + 1)/(2x + 1)(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 6)(x + 2)\n3(x + 2) + (x + 6) \u003d 3(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 2) + (x + 6) - 3(x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 9) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-9\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(x + 6) + 1/(x + 2) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(x + 6)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-10", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(x + 6)\n3(x + 6)/2 + (x + 2) \u003d 2(x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 6)/2 + (x + 2) - 2(x + 3) \u003d 0\n(x + 10)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-10\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/2(x + 2) + 1/(x + 6) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(x + 2)(x + 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-13", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 5)\n3(x + 5)/2 + 2(x + 1) \u003d 3(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 5)/2 + 2(x + 1) - 3(x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 13)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-13\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/2(x + 1) + 2/(x + 5) \u003d 3/(x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 7)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + (2x + 7)/3 \u003d 2(x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + (2x + 7)/3 - 2(x + 2) \u003d 0\n(-x - 2)/3 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(2x + 7) + 1/3(x + 1) \u003d 2(x + 2)/(2x + 7)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 3)(x + 1)\n3(x + 1)/2 + (x + 3)/3 \u003d 2(x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 1)/2 + (x + 3)/3 - 2(x + 2) \u003d 0\n(-x - 9)/6 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-9\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/2(x + 3) + 1/3(x + 1) \u003d 2(x + 2)/(x + 3)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-14", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 4)(x + 7)\n3(x + 7) + 2(x + 4) \u003d (3x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 7) + 2(x + 4) - (3x + 1) \u003d 0\n2(x + 14) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-14\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(x + 4) + 2/(x + 7) \u003d (3x + 1)/(x + 4)(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 3)(3x + 2)\n2(3x + 2) + 3(x + 3) \u003d (3x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(3x + 2) + 3(x + 3) - (3x + 1) \u003d 0\n6(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(x + 3) + 3/(3x + 2) \u003d (3x + 1)/(x + 3)(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-17", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 6)(x + 5)\n3(x + 5) + (x + 6) \u003d (3x + 4)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 5) + (x + 6) - (3x + 4) \u003d 0\n(x + 17) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-17\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(x + 6) + 1/(x + 5) \u003d (3x + 4)/(x + 6)(x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(2x + 7)\n(2x + 7) + (x + 1) \u003d 2(x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 7) + (x + 1) - 2(x + 3) \u003d 0\n(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 1/(2x + 7) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(x + 1)(2x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 1)(x + 2)\n(x + 2) + 3(2x + 1) \u003d (x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 2) + 3(2x + 1) - (x + 5) \u003d 0\n6(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(2x + 1) + 3/(x + 2) \u003d (x + 5)/(2x + 1)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 5)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + 3(x + 5)/2 \u003d 2(x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + 3(x + 5)/2 - 2(x + 2) \u003d 0\n(x + 9)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-9\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 5) + 3/2(x + 1) \u003d 2(x + 2)/(x + 5)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 3)(2x + 3)\n(2x + 3) + (2x + 3) \u003d (3x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 3) + (2x + 3) - (3x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 5) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-5\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(2x + 3) + 1/(2x + 3) \u003d (3x + 1)/(2x + 3)(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 4)(x + 2)\n(x + 2) + (x + 4)/2 \u003d (x + 6)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 2) + (x + 4)/2 - (x + 6) \u003d 0\n(x - 4)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n4\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 4) + 1/2(x + 2) \u003d (x + 6)/(x + 4)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(3x + 1)\n(3x + 1) + 2(x + 1) \u003d (x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(3x + 1) + 2(x + 1) - (x + 3) \u003d 0\n4(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 2/(3x + 1) \u003d (x + 3)/(x + 1)(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 7)\n(x + 7)/3 + (x + 1) \u003d 2(x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 7)/3 + (x + 1) - 2(x + 3) \u003d 0\n-2(x + 4)/3 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-4\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/3(x + 1) + 1/(x + 7) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(x + 1)(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(3x + 5)\n(3x + 5) + 3(x + 2) \u003d (3x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(3x + 5) + 3(x + 2) - (3x + 2) \u003d 0\n3(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 2) + 3/(3x + 5) \u003d (3x + 2)/(x + 2)(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 4)\n3(x + 4) + 2(x + 1) \u003d (2x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 4) + 2(x + 1) - (2x + 5) \u003d 0\n3(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(x + 1) + 2/(x + 4) \u003d (2x + 5)/(x + 1)(x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 3)(x + 2)\n(x + 2) + (x + 3) \u003d (x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 2) + (x + 3) - (x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 4) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-4\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 3) + 1/(x + 2) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 3)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 5)(2x + 1)\n(2x + 1) + (x + 5) \u003d (x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 1) + (x + 5) - (x + 2) \u003d 0\n2(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 5) + 1/(2x + 1) \u003d (x + 2)/(x + 5)(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-10", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 1)(x + 7)\n3(x + 7) + (2x + 1) \u003d (3x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 7) + (2x + 1) - (3x + 2) \u003d 0\n2(x + 10) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-10\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(2x + 1) + 1/(x + 7) \u003d (3x + 2)/(2x + 1)(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 6)\n(x + 1) + 3(x + 6)/2 \u003d 3(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + 3(x + 6)/2 - 3(x + 1) \u003d 0\n(-x + 14)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n14\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 6) + 3/2(x + 1) \u003d 3/(x + 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 3)(x + 3)\n2(x + 3) + 2(2x + 3) \u003d 2(x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 3) + 2(2x + 3) - 2(x + 2) \u003d 0\n4(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(2x + 3) + 2/(x + 3) \u003d 2(x + 2)/(2x + 3)(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 2)(3x + 1)\n3(3x + 1) + (3x + 2) \u003d (x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(3x + 1) + (3x + 2) - (x + 5) \u003d 0\n11(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(3x + 2) + 1/(3x + 1) \u003d (x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 3)(3x + 4)\n(3x + 4)/2 + 3(x + 3) \u003d (3x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(3x + 4)/2 + 3(x + 3) - (3x + 2) \u003d 0\n3(x + 6)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-6\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/2(x + 3) + 3/(3x + 4) \u003d (3x + 2)/(x + 3)(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 3)(x + 2)\n3(x + 2)/2 + (x + 3)/3 \u003d (x + 4)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 2)/2 + (x + 3)/3 - (x + 4) \u003d 0\n5(x)/6 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/2(x + 3) + 1/3(x + 2) \u003d (x + 4)/(x + 3)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(x + 2)\n(x + 2) + (x + 2)/2 \u003d 2(x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 2) + (x + 2)/2 - 2(x + 3) \u003d 0\n(-x - 6)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-6\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 2) + 1/2(x + 2) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(x + 2)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 3)\n3(x + 3)/2 + (x + 1)/2 \u003d (3x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 3)/2 + (x + 1)/2 - (3x + 2) \u003d 0\n(-x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/2(x + 1) + 1/2(x + 3) \u003d (3x + 2)/(x + 1)(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(2x + 7)\n(2x + 7)/3 + (x + 2) \u003d 2(x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 7)/3 + (x + 2) - 2(x + 3) \u003d 0\n(-x - 5)/3 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-5\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/3(x + 2) + 1/(2x + 7) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(x + 2)(2x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 4)(2x + 1)\n(2x + 1) + 2(x + 4) \u003d 3(x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 1) + 2(x + 4) - 3(x + 2) \u003d 0\n(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 4) + 2/(2x + 1) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(x + 4)(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(x + 2)\n2(x + 2) + (x + 2) \u003d 2(x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 2) + (x + 2) - 2(x + 3) \u003d 0\nx \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(x + 2) + 1/(x + 2) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(x + 2)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-12", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 6)(x + 2)\n3(x + 2) + (x + 6)/2 \u003d 3(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 2) + (x + 6)/2 - 3(x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 12)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-12\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(x + 6) + 1/2(x + 2) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(x + 6)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 5)\n2(3x + 4) + 2(2x + 5) \u003d (3x + 4)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(3x + 4) + 2(2x + 5) - (3x + 4) \u003d 0\n7(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(2x + 5) + 2/(3x + 4) \u003d 1/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 5)(2x + 5)\n(2x + 5) + (2x + 5) \u003d 2(x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 5) + (2x + 5) - 2(x + 3) \u003d 0\n2(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(2x + 5) + 1/(2x + 5) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(2x + 5)(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 4)(x + 1)\n3(x + 1) + (3x + 4) \u003d (3x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 1) + (3x + 4) - (3x + 1) \u003d 0\n3(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(3x + 4) + 1/(x + 1) \u003d (3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 1)(x + 5)\n2(x + 5) + (3x + 1) \u003d 3(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 5) + (3x + 1) - 3(x + 1) \u003d 0\n2(x + 4) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-4\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(3x + 1) + 1/(x + 5) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(3x + 1)(x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 4)(x + 2)\n2(x + 2) + (3x + 4) \u003d (2x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 2) + (3x + 4) - (2x + 5) \u003d 0\n3(x + 1) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(3x + 4) + 1/(x + 2) \u003d (2x + 5)/(3x + 4)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(3x + 7)\n(3x + 7) + 3(x + 1) \u003d (3x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(3x + 7) + 3(x + 1) - (3x + 1) \u003d 0\n3(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 3/(3x + 7) \u003d (3x + 1)/(x + 1)(3x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(x + 4)\n3(x + 4)/2 + (x + 2) \u003d 3(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 4)/2 + (x + 2) - 3(x + 1) \u003d 0\n(-x + 10)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n10\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/2(x + 2) + 1/(x + 4) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(x + 2)(x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 1)(x + 1)\n2(x + 1) + 2(2x + 1) \u003d (x + 4)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 1) + 2(2x + 1) - (x + 4) \u003d 0\n5(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(2x + 1) + 2/(x + 1) \u003d (x + 4)/(2x + 1)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 5)\n(x + 5) + (x + 1) \u003d (x + 4)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 5) + (x + 1) - (x + 4) \u003d 0\n(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 1/(x + 5) \u003d (x + 4)/(x + 1)(x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 1)(2x + 5)\n(2x + 5) + (3x + 1) \u003d (x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 5) + (3x + 1) - (x + 2) \u003d 0\n4(x + 1) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(3x + 1) + 1/(2x + 5) \u003d (x + 2)/(3x + 1)(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 1)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + 2(2x + 1) \u003d (3x + 7)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + 2(2x + 1) - (3x + 7) \u003d 0\n2(x - 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(2x + 1) + 2/(x + 1) \u003d (3x + 7)/(2x + 1)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 4)\n(x + 1) + 2(x + 4) \u003d 2(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + 2(x + 4) - 2(x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 7) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-7\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 4) + 2/(x + 1) \u003d 2/(x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 1)(3x + 4)\n(3x + 4) + (2x + 1) \u003d (3x + 7)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(3x + 4) + (2x + 1) - (3x + 7) \u003d 0\n2(x - 1) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(2x + 1) + 1/(3x + 4) \u003d (3x + 7)/(2x + 1)(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 1)\n2(x + 1)/3 + 3(x + 1)/2 \u003d 2(x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 1)/3 + 3(x + 1)/2 - 2(x + 2) \u003d 0\n(x - 11)/6 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n11\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/3(x + 1) + 3/2(x + 1) \u003d 2(x + 2)/(x + 1)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 1)(x + 3)\n(x + 3) + (3x + 1)/2 \u003d (2x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 3) + (3x + 1)/2 - (2x + 3) \u003d 0\n(x + 1)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(3x + 1) + 1/2(x + 3) \u003d (2x + 3)/(3x + 1)(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(2x + 1)\n(2x + 1) + 2(x + 1) \u003d (x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 1) + 2(x + 1) - (x + 3) \u003d 0\n3(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 2/(2x + 1) \u003d (x + 3)/(x + 1)(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 6)\n(x + 6)/2 + (x + 1) \u003d (3x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 6)/2 + (x + 1) - (3x + 1) \u003d 0\n-3(x - 2)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/2(x + 1) + 1/(x + 6) \u003d (3x + 1)/(x + 1)(x + 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 2)(x + 2)\n(x + 2) + (3x + 2) \u003d (3x + 7)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 2) + (3x + 2) - (3x + 7) \u003d 0\n(x - 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(3x + 2) + 1/(x + 2) \u003d (3x + 7)/(3x + 2)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 3)(2x + 1)\n2(2x + 1) + (2x + 3) \u003d (3x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(2x + 1) + (2x + 3) - (3x + 5) \u003d 0\n3(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(2x + 3) + 1/(2x + 1) \u003d (3x + 5)/(2x + 3)(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(3x + 5)\n(3x + 5) + (x + 1) \u003d (x + 6)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(3x + 5) + (x + 1) - (x + 6) \u003d 0\n3(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 1/(3x + 5) \u003d (x + 6)/(x + 1)(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 2)(x + 3)\n(x + 3) + (3x + 2)/2 \u003d (3x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 3) + (3x + 2)/2 - (3x + 1) \u003d 0\n(-x + 6)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n6\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(3x + 2) + 1/2(x + 3) \u003d (3x + 1)/(3x + 2)(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 5)(3x + 1)\n2(3x + 1) + (3x + 5) \u003d (x + 7)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(3x + 1) + (3x + 5) - (x + 7) \u003d 0\n8(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(3x + 5) + 1/(3x + 1) \u003d (x + 7)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 6)(3x + 4)\n(3x + 4) + (x + 6) \u003d (3x + 7)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(3x + 4) + (x + 6) - (3x + 7) \u003d 0\n(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 6) + 1/(3x + 4) \u003d (3x + 7)/(x + 6)(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(x + 1)\n2(x + 1) + 2(x + 2)/3 \u003d (3x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 1) + 2(x + 2)/3 - (3x + 2) \u003d 0\n(-x + 4)/3 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n4\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(x + 2) + 2/3(x + 1) \u003d (3x + 2)/(x + 2)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 5)(x + 5)\n2(x + 5) + 3(x + 5) \u003d (x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 5) + 3(x + 5) - (x + 1) \u003d 0\n4(x + 6) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-6\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(x + 5) + 3/(x + 5) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 5)(x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 3)(x + 3)\n(x + 3) + (x + 3) \u003d (x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 3) + (x + 3) - (x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 5) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-5\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 3) + 1/(x + 3) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 3)(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 6)(2x + 1)\n(2x + 1) + 2(x + 6) \u003d (x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 1) + 2(x + 6) - (x + 1) \u003d 0\n3(x + 4) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-4\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 6) + 2/(2x + 1) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 6)(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 2)(3x + 7)\n3(3x + 7) + (3x + 2) \u003d (2x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(3x + 7) + (3x + 2) - (2x + 3) \u003d 0\n10(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(3x + 2) + 1/(3x + 7) \u003d (2x + 3)/(3x + 2)(3x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 3)\n3(x + 3)/2 + 2(x + 1) \u003d (3x + 4)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 3)/2 + 2(x + 1) - (3x + 4) \u003d 0\n(x + 5)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-5\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/2(x + 1) + 2/(x + 3) \u003d (3x + 4)/(x + 1)(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(x + 5)\n(x + 5) + 2(x + 2) \u003d (x + 7)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 5) + 2(x + 2) - (x + 7) \u003d 0\n2(x + 1) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 2) + 2/(x + 5) \u003d (x + 7)/(x + 2)(x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 3)(x + 1)\n2(x + 1) + 2(x + 3)/3 \u003d (x + 4)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 1) + 2(x + 3)/3 - (x + 4) \u003d 0\n5(x)/3 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(x + 3) + 2/3(x + 1) \u003d (x + 4)/(x + 3)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 4)(x + 3)\n2(x + 3) + (x + 4) \u003d 2(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 3) + (x + 4) - 2(x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 8) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-8\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(x + 4) + 1/(x + 3) \u003d 2(x + 1)/(x + 4)(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 5)(2x + 1)\n(2x + 1) + (3x + 5) \u003d (x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 1) + (3x + 5) - (x + 2) \u003d 0\n4(x + 1) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(3x + 5) + 1/(2x + 1) \u003d (x + 2)/(3x + 5)(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 2)\n(x + 2) + 2(x + 1)/3 \u003d (x + 6)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 2) + 2(x + 1)/3 - (x + 6) \u003d 0\n2(x - 5)/3 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n5\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 2/3(x + 2) \u003d (x + 6)/(x + 1)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + 3(x + 1) \u003d (3x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + 3(x + 1) - (3x + 2) \u003d 0\n(x + 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 3/(x + 1) \u003d (3x + 2)/(x + 1)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 1)(3x + 4)\n(3x + 4) + (2x + 1) \u003d (2x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(3x + 4) + (2x + 1) - (2x + 5) \u003d 0\n3(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(2x + 1) + 1/(3x + 4) \u003d (2x + 5)/(2x + 1)(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 2)(x + 7)\n3(x + 7) + 2(3x + 2) \u003d (x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 7) + 2(3x + 2) - (x + 1) \u003d 0\n8(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(3x + 2) + 2/(x + 7) \u003d (x + 1)/(3x + 2)(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 1)(2x + 1)\n(2x + 1) + (2x + 1) \u003d (x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 1) + (2x + 1) - (x + 2) \u003d 0\n3(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(2x + 1) + 1/(2x + 1) \u003d (x + 2)/(2x + 1)(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 1)(x + 1)\n2(x + 1) + (3x + 1)/2 \u003d (x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 1) + (3x + 1)/2 - (x + 5) \u003d 0\n5(x - 1)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(3x + 1) + 1/2(x + 1) \u003d (x + 5)/(3x + 1)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 6)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + 2(x + 6) \u003d 2(x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + 2(x + 6) - 2(x + 3) \u003d 0\n(x + 7) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-7\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 6) + 2/(x + 1) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(x + 6)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 5)\n(x + 2) + (3x + 5)/2 \u003d 2(x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 2) + (3x + 5)/2 - 2(x + 2) \u003d 0\n(x + 1)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(3x + 5) + 1/2(x + 2) \u003d 2/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 6)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + (x + 6) \u003d (3x + 7)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + (x + 6) - (3x + 7) \u003d 0\n-x \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 6) + 1/(x + 1) \u003d (3x + 7)/(x + 6)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 6)(x + 6)\n(x + 6) + (x + 6) \u003d (x + 7)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 6) + (x + 6) - (x + 7) \u003d 0\n(x + 5) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-5\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 6) + 1/(x + 6) \u003d (x + 7)/(x + 6)(x + 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 4)(x + 7)\n2(x + 7) + 2(3x + 4) \u003d (3x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 7) + 2(3x + 4) - (3x + 2) \u003d 0\n5(x + 4) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-4\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(3x + 4) + 2/(x + 7) \u003d (3x + 2)/(3x + 4)(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + (x + 1)/2 \u003d 2(x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + (x + 1)/2 - 2(x + 3) \u003d 0\n(-x - 9)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-9\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 1/2(x + 1) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(x + 1)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 7)(2x + 7)\n2(2x + 7) + (3x + 7) \u003d (x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(2x + 7) + (3x + 7) - (x + 3) \u003d 0\n6(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(3x + 7) + 1/(2x + 7) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x + 7)(2x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 1)(2x + 1)\n2(2x + 1) + (3x + 1) \u003d (x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(2x + 1) + (3x + 1) - (x + 3) \u003d 0\n6(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(3x + 1) + 1/(2x + 1) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x + 1)(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 3)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + (2x + 3) \u003d (x + 6)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + (2x + 3) - (x + 6) \u003d 0\n2(x - 1) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n1\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(2x + 3) + 1/(x + 1) \u003d (x + 6)/(2x + 3)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(2x + 3)\n(2x + 3) + 2(x + 1) \u003d (3x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 3) + 2(x + 1) - (3x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 4) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-4\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 2/(2x + 3) \u003d (3x + 1)/(x + 1)(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 4)(3x + 4)\n(3x + 4) + 2(x + 4) \u003d (2x + 3)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(3x + 4) + 2(x + 4) - (2x + 3) \u003d 0\n3(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 4) + 2/(3x + 4) \u003d (2x + 3)/(x + 4)(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 1)\n2(x + 2) + 2(3x + 1) \u003d 3(x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 2) + 2(3x + 1) - 3(x + 2) \u003d 0\n5(x) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n0\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(3x + 1) + 2/(x + 2) \u003d 3/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(x + 2)\n3(x + 2) + (x + 2) \u003d 3(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 2) + (x + 2) - 3(x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 5) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-5\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(x + 2) + 1/(x + 2) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(x + 2)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 7)(x + 2)\n2(x + 2) + (x + 7) \u003d (2x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 2) + (x + 7) - (2x + 5) \u003d 0\n(x + 6) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-6\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(x + 7) + 1/(x + 2) \u003d (2x + 5)/(x + 7)(x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 4)(x + 3)\n2(x + 3) + (x + 4)/2 \u003d (2x + 5)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n2(x + 3) + (x + 4)/2 - (2x + 5) \u003d 0\n(x + 6)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-6\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2/(x + 4) + 1/2(x + 3) \u003d (2x + 5)/(x + 4)(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(2x + 7)\n(2x + 7)/3 + 2(x + 2) \u003d (3x + 2)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(2x + 7)/3 + 2(x + 2) - (3x + 2) \u003d 0\n(-x + 13)/3 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n13\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/3(x + 2) + 2/(2x + 7) \u003d (3x + 2)/(x + 2)(2x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 1)(x + 1)\n(x + 1) + (x + 1) \u003d (x + 4)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 1) + (x + 1) - (x + 4) \u003d 0\n(x - 2) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n2\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(x + 1) + 1/(x + 1) \u003d (x + 4)/(x + 1)(x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(3x + 1)(x + 3)\n(x + 3) + (3x + 1)/2 \u003d (2x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n(x + 3) + (3x + 1)/2 - (2x + 1) \u003d 0\n(x + 5)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-5\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n1/(3x + 1) + 1/2(x + 3) \u003d (2x + 1)/(3x + 1)(x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(2x + 1)(x + 7)\n3(x + 7) + 2(2x + 1) \u003d 3(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 7) + 2(2x + 1) - 3(x + 1) \u003d 0\n4(x + 5) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-5\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(2x + 1) + 2/(x + 7) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(2x + 1)(x + 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 5)\n3(x + 1) + (x + 5) \u003d 2(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 1) + (x + 5) - 2(x + 1) \u003d 0\n2(x + 3) \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-3\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(x + 5) + 1/(x + 1) \u003d 2/(x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "Multiply through by the least common polynomial of the rational expressions,\n(x + 2)(x + 3)\n3(x + 3) + 3(x + 2)/2 \u003d 3(x + 1)\nMove all terms onto the same side of the equation\n3(x + 3) + 3(x + 2)/2 - 3(x + 1) \u003d 0\n3(x + 6)/2 \u003d 0\nSolve the simplified expression for x\n-6\nCheck that the answer is valid", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3/(x + 2) + 3/2(x + 3) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(x + 2)(x + 3)", "type": "text"}
]}